https://mainecul.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Home :: Privacy Policy
Print
At the Maine Credit Union League, we respect your privacy.  By using this website (the “Site”), you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and you consent to our data use and collection practices described below.  If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact Tim Brooks.
1. Information You Provide to Us
We may collect and store your personal information when you visit this Site, register an account with us, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a survey, campaign, contest or promotion.  For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, your personal information may include your name, address, phone number, email address, account user ID and password, gender and other identifying information you provide to us.  Submitting personal information is voluntary, but you may not be able to take advantage of all of our services and features if you do not provide us will all of the requested information.
2. General Information Areas
To track site use, measure site traffic, and improve site navigation and information, we collect basic information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, dates and times of this Site visits.
We use cookies.  You may control permissions for cookies on this or any other website by adjusting your individual browser settings for customized privacy protection.
3.  Use of Your Information
Without disclosing your personal information to third parties, we may use it to enhance the quality of our services and of the content of this Site, as well as to communicate with you via email, by mail, by phone and by other means about our services, membership programs, campaigns and promotions, unless you opt out of our promotional communications.  If you do not wish to receive any promotional communications from us, please let us know by following simple instructions contained in such communications or by contacting Tim Brooks.
If you send us an email, we may use your feedback to respond to other inquiries, comments or suggestions without disclosing your personal information.
4. Privacy of Your Information
We respect your privacy and will not share, sell or disclose your personal information to any third parties without first receiving your permission except as follows.  We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law; to exercise our legal rights; or if we determine that such disclosure is necessary to prevent, investigate or address suspected illegal activities or fraud.
5.  We Protect Your Information
We have implemented electronic, physical and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information.  In addition to using security software, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons.  PGP protocol encrypts registration information when you submit it. Further, our business practices are reviewed periodically for compliance with policies and procedures governing the security and confidentiality of our information.
6.  Security of this Site
For site security purposes, this Site employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this Site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1987 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.
7.  Children
This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13.
8. Links to Third-Party Sites
For your convenience, this website contains links to third party sites, including social media sites.  By clicking or otherwise following a link to any site other than this Site, you become subject to the privacy policy of that site.  Except for information posted by us, we do not endorse the views expressed or the facts presented on any third party site and do not endorse any commercial products that may be advertised on any third party site.  All social media sites and applications, including Facebook, Youtube, Twitter and Instagram, referenced on this Site are controlled and administered by a third party and have different privacy policies from this Site.  We disclaim any liability for any loss or damage resulting from your use of any third party sites.  If you visit another site, we encourage you to read that particular site’s privacy policy.
9. Effective Date
This Privacy Policy was updated on 1/7/14.
Access Your Credit Union
Over 170 locations in Maine and more
than 5,900 locations nationwide
Learn moreFind a Credit Union
Learn moreSurcharge-free access atnearly 270 CU24 SURF locations
Find a Location
Email a Friend
CLOSE
